{
    "id": "c0c9138561114264aa5e8d3914d4ea8f",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ..................... him for the past month.",
            "description": "The present perfect is more common with the time expressions for and since.",
            "answers": [
                "haven't met",
                "didn't meet",
                "hadn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b51b46b77dd24bacb0fe355423cee508"
        },
        {
            "question": "Professionals ..................... doctors and teachers are more useful than artists.",
            "description": "We use such as to give examples.",
            "answers": [
                "such as",
                "such that",
                "such"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b695fcf05adc4c1194a48add8a85934d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl ....................... walked in right now is my niece.",
            "description": "We use who to refer to people.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5bb258b3c29d4fca98e0e8852f292f5f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Something .......................... be done to improve the situation.",
            "description": "Ought is followed by an infinitive with to. Ought to is similar to should.",
            "answers": [
                "ought to",
                "ought",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a0df59cf3b21433a8b94592284c4353a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ......................... leave him alone.",
            "description": "Must is a modal auxiliary. Questions and negatives are made without do.",
            "answers": [
                "must not",
                "don't must",
                "not must"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dabaf66de85b42d9a71fabe21915c352"
        },
        {
            "question": "I opened the door but I didn't see ......................",
            "description": "Not anybody means the same as nobody.",
            "answers": [
                "anybody",
                "nobody",
                "any body"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "228d0578a400419fb9862a9964791efb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I rang the doorbell six times but ........................ opened the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anybody",
                "nobody",
                "no body"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81c3d348f173489eb828acb515162c68"
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn't ........................... recognize me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "rather",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "11ba0d6398a54ad5988af4207ddb0fa3"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the .......................... movie I have seen.",
            "description": "Worst is the superlative form of bad.",
            "answers": [
                "worse",
                "baddest",
                "worst"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9eed65c1fdb9424699a0cadb63e7cd0a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We got into trouble …………………………. your stupidity.",
            "description": "Because of is a preposition. It is used before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f2b306604eee4272abb43a58cb7637bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked ………………………. the best of his ability.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d732fda7d02c428a91e25d4f773a3446"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cain struck Abel …………………………… he was jealous of him.",
            "description": "Because is a conjunction. It is used before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "63b2ad78221840cfa0b635a138cf9b0b"
        }
    ]
}